<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/project/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/project/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-01T11:21:35+02:00</updated><id>/project/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Snooker Blog</title><subtitle>The snooker is an amazing game!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Murphy Stunned By China’s Chen</title><link href="/project/2018/11/29/murphy-loss.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Murphy Stunned By China’s Chen" /><published>2018-11-29T08:30:03+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T08:30:03+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/29/murphy-loss</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/29/murphy-loss.html">&lt;h3&gt; Murphy Stunned By China’s Chen&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;left&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/murphy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Shaun Murphy, champion ten years ago, suffered a shock 6-3 defeat against world number 124 Chen Feilong in the first round of the Betway UK Championship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Murphy has had a disappointing start to the 2018/19 campaign, failing to go beyond the last 16 of a ranking event, but this was the most surprising defeat of his season so far. He took the UK title in 2008 and was runner-up in 2012 and 2017, but this time the world number nine misses out on the TV stages in York.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/chen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Chen, age 36, is playing on the pro tour for the first time this season and had only won one match previously, but he played some excellent snooker today. From 3-1 down, he knocked in breaks of 54, 88, 54 and 49 to go 5-3 ahead, before sealing victory in a tense ninth frame by potting the last blue and pink. He goes through to the last 64 to face Martin O’Donnell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Murphy said: “I didn’t see that coming because I have been practising so hard, my preparation for this event has been fantastic. I have had a terrible season so far but that has left me a lot of time to practise and I feel my game is in such good shape. But I’m still waiting for that to come through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Chen played some great snooker after the interval and he deserved it in the end. He potted some outrageous balls when I had him in the long grass. I thought he might twitch a bit towards the end, but he didn’t. I can’t wallow in self-pity and give up, I have to keep on going.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ryan Day, ranked 12th, was another top 16 player to head for the exit door as he lost 6-2 to world number 121 Joe O’Connor. Leicester’s 23-year-old O’Connor, another tour debutant, made a top break of 55 as he got the better of an out-of-sorts Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O’Connor said: “It’s definitely the best win of my career so far. Surprisingly I didn’t get nervous towards the end, I have played on the match table here a couple of times before so that helped. It’s massive for my confidence because it shows I can beat the top players. I will always think back to this day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/mfu1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Marco Fu kept up his hopes of a place in the Masters by beating Hammad Miah 6-0 with a top break of 101. As it stands, Fu is 17th in the Race to the Masters so he must reach at least the last 16 in York otherwise he will miss snooker’s biggest invitation event for the first time since 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was really nervous today because the UK Championship is a big event and I have been struggling so far this season,” said Hong Kong’s Fu, who missed several months of snooker after having laser eye surgery earlier this year. “Sometimes you can try too desperately to do well. After the first couple of frames I settled down a bit, tried to play a bit quicker and just let it happen rather than worrying too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My eyes are still recovering from the surgery, I am waiting for the retina to settle. I still see black spots, some days it’s worse than others. I try to take it easy on my eyes by not practising too much but at this level you have to be 100% ready for every tournament. So it’s difficult, but I just need to win a few matches, a good run might be around the corner. I am not thinking about the Masters, if I’m not in it it will be my own fault because I haven’t been playing well.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stuart Bingham ended a run of three consecutive defeats by beating James Wattana 6-0. Bingham won the English Open last month then suffered a dip in form but looked back in shape today as breaks of 92 and 78 helped him to a comfortable victory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Perry was another 6-0 winner as he white-washed John Astley with a top run of 143 – the new front-runner for the £5,000 high break prize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perry reached the final of the European Masters last month before losing to Jimmy Robertson.  “I was really disappointed to lose that match,” Perry reflected today. “Not because they way I played, just because I lost. It was the first final I had ever started as favourite and it was a big opportunity. That knocked me back a bit and I’ve had a few poor results since. But today was the best I have played in a long time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Swail came from 5-3 down to beat Michael White 6-5 while Tom Ford made a 119 in a 6-5 win over Craig Steadman. Eden Sharav came from 5-1 down to 5-5 against Sunny Akani, only for Thailand’s Akani to win the decider with a run of 67.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Murphy Stunned By China’s Chen Shaun Murphy, champion ten years ago, suffered a shock 6-3 defeat against world number 124 Chen Feilong in the first round of the Betway UK Championship.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lucky Higgins Edges Out Poomjaeng</title><link href="/project/2018/11/29/lucky-higgins.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lucky Higgins Edges Out Poomjaeng" /><published>2018-11-29T06:23:03+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T06:23:03+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/29/lucky-higgins</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/29/lucky-higgins.html">&lt;h3&gt;Lucky Higgins Edges Out Poomjaeng&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/higgins.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    After the shock exits of Shaun Murphy and Ryan Day earlier in the day Higgins looked in danger of becoming another high profile casualty in the first round in York when he frittered away leads of 4-1 and 5-3. He made a break of 101 in the fourth frame but otherwise struggled for fluency as Thailand’s Poomjaeng battled back to 5-5.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Amateur cueman Poomjaeng had two early chances in the deciding frame but missed one red to a centre pocket and another to a baulk corner. Gritty Higgins made a crucial break of 60 which proved enough for victory in a match which finished at 12.30am. Three-time UK Champion Higgins now faces a tartan tussle against Alan McManus in the last 64.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s the way I have been playing all season, it’s no surprise to me how badly I struggled there,” said 43-year-old Higgins. “I was really lucky because Dechawat had a good chance in the last frame, if he had potted the red to the middle I would have fancied him to make a frame-winning break because all the balls were there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know how I’ll play in the next game against Alan but I’ll look forward to it. There is no one who has more respect for Alan than me, I have learned a lot from him and I know how tough he is.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;left&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/allen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Mark Allen enjoyed a comfortable 6-2 win over Basem Eltahhan, compiling runs of 97, 126, 73 and 128. His next opponent will be Peter Lines or Rory McLeod.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a potential banana skin out of the way,” said world number seven Allen, who won his fourth ranking title at the International Championship earlier this month. “I scored when I got chances but I will need to play a lot better in the next round.  I feel as if I am one of the contenders this year, which I haven’t been over the last few years. I just hope I am still here this time next week.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thailand’s Thepchaiya Un-Nooh beat Jimmy White 6-3 with top breaks of 81, 84, 83 and 110. Local favourite Paul Davison, from Pickering, saw off Stuart Carrington 6-1 with a top run of 77.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;European Masters champion Jimmy Robertson made a 133 in a 6-4 win over Jordan Brown while Yushan World Open finalist David Gilbert top scored with 128 and 122 in a  6-3 win over Ashley Carty.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Lucky Higgins Edges Out Poomjaeng After the shock exits of Shaun Murphy and Ryan Day earlier in the day Higgins looked in danger of becoming another high profile casualty in the first round in York when he frittered away leads of 4-1 and 5-3. He made a break of 101 in the fourth frame but otherwise struggled for fluency as Thailand’s Poomjaeng battled back to 5-5. Amateur cueman Poomjaeng had two early chances in the deciding frame but missed one red to a centre pocket and another to a baulk corner. Gritty Higgins made a crucial break of 60 which proved enough for victory in a match which finished at 12.30am. Three-time UK Champion Higgins now faces a tartan tussle against Alan McManus in the last 64. “That’s the way I have been playing all season, it’s no surprise to me how badly I struggled there,” said 43-year-old Higgins. “I was really lucky because Dechawat had a good chance in the last frame, if he had potted the red to the middle I would have fancied him to make a frame-winning break because all the balls were there. “I don’t know how I’ll play in the next game against Alan but I’ll look forward to it. There is no one who has more respect for Alan than me, I have learned a lot from him and I know how tough he is.” Mark Allen enjoyed a comfortable 6-2 win over Basem Eltahhan, compiling runs of 97, 126, 73 and 128. His next opponent will be Peter Lines or Rory McLeod. “It’s a potential banana skin out of the way,” said world number seven Allen, who won his fourth ranking title at the International Championship earlier this month. “I scored when I got chances but I will need to play a lot better in the next round. I feel as if I am one of the contenders this year, which I haven’t been over the last few years. I just hope I am still here this time next week.” Thailand’s Thepchaiya Un-Nooh beat Jimmy White 6-3 with top breaks of 81, 84, 83 and 110. Local favourite Paul Davison, from Pickering, saw off Stuart Carrington 6-1 with a top run of 77. European Masters champion Jimmy Robertson made a 133 in a 6-4 win over Jordan Brown while Yushan World Open finalist David Gilbert top scored with 128 and 122 in a 6-3 win over Ashley Carty.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Selby Crashes Against Amateur Cahill</title><link href="/project/2018/11/29/selby-crashes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Selby Crashes Against Amateur Cahill" /><published>2018-11-29T05:05:03+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T05:05:03+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/29/selby-crashes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/29/selby-crashes.html">&lt;h3&gt;Selby Crashes Against Amateur Cahill &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;World number one Mark Selby was the victim of the one of the biggest shocks in Betway UK Championship history as he lost 6-3 to amateur James Cahill in the first round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three-time World and two-time UK Champion Selby was one of the favourites for the title but failed to even make it to the TV stages in York as he was outplayed by 22-year-old Cahill, who was handed a place in the 128-man field as one of the leading ‘top-ups’ from the Q School ranking list. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is familiar territory for Cahill as he beat Ding Junhui on the way to the last 16 of the same tournament four years ago. He subsequently dropped off the pro tour in 2017 but showed today he still has the ability and temperament to compete on the big stage. The Blackpool cueman goes through to the last 64 to face Sunny Akani.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;left&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/cahill.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Cahill won the first four frames with a top break of 70. Selby pulled one back and had chances in frame six but missed a short-range final pink to a centre pocket, allowing his opponent to go 5-1 ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A scrappy seventh frame went Selby’s way then he made a 103 to close to 5-3. The ninth came down to a safety battle on the final pink, and Cahill converted a brilliant pot along the length of a side cushion to seal victory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mark didn’t play as well as he can, but even at 5-1 up against him you know there’s still a match on,” said Cahill. “In the last frame I thought if I got a chance on the pink I’d just go for it because you don’t want to be in a safety battle against Mark. I didn’t feel nervous after the first frame, there was more pressure on Mark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In my last season on tour I used 11 different cues, I was all over the place and losing games. After that I had some time away from snooker because I had been playing every day for ten years. Now I’m back into it, I’ve got good people around me and I’m practising hard. I feel I am playing better now than I have done in the past. I feel as if I am good enough to compete with the best and I have proved that a few times, I just need to show more consistency.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selby is now in danger of losing his world number one spot for the first time since February 2015. If Mark Williams goes all the way to the title in York he will go top of the rankings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/selby.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Leicester’s Selby said: “I was rubbish all match, I didn’t get going at all. I’m devastated because it’s a big tournament. I felt flat and couldn’t get myself up for the match which is strange because it’s such a big event. If I had potted the pink to go 4-2 I probably would have won because he was wilting at that stage. I have been playing really well lately so to perform like that is a real surprise for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;World Champion Williams had no such trouble as he beat Adam Duffy 6-2 with a top break of 68.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This will probably be my last tournament of the year so I’ll try to have a good run,” said Williams. “The last few months have been a bit of a party for me. I’m going on holiday in December and then when I get back before the Masters I will have to knuckle down and get back to normal.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Selby Crashes Against Amateur Cahill World number one Mark Selby was the victim of the one of the biggest shocks in Betway UK Championship history as he lost 6-3 to amateur James Cahill in the first round. Three-time World and two-time UK Champion Selby was one of the favourites for the title but failed to even make it to the TV stages in York as he was outplayed by 22-year-old Cahill, who was handed a place in the 128-man field as one of the leading ‘top-ups’ from the Q School ranking list. This is familiar territory for Cahill as he beat Ding Junhui on the way to the last 16 of the same tournament four years ago. He subsequently dropped off the pro tour in 2017 but showed today he still has the ability and temperament to compete on the big stage. The Blackpool cueman goes through to the last 64 to face Sunny Akani. Cahill won the first four frames with a top break of 70. Selby pulled one back and had chances in frame six but missed a short-range final pink to a centre pocket, allowing his opponent to go 5-1 ahead. A scrappy seventh frame went Selby’s way then he made a 103 to close to 5-3. The ninth came down to a safety battle on the final pink, and Cahill converted a brilliant pot along the length of a side cushion to seal victory. “Mark didn’t play as well as he can, but even at 5-1 up against him you know there’s still a match on,” said Cahill. “In the last frame I thought if I got a chance on the pink I’d just go for it because you don’t want to be in a safety battle against Mark. I didn’t feel nervous after the first frame, there was more pressure on Mark. “In my last season on tour I used 11 different cues, I was all over the place and losing games. After that I had some time away from snooker because I had been playing every day for ten years. Now I’m back into it, I’ve got good people around me and I’m practising hard. I feel I am playing better now than I have done in the past. I feel as if I am good enough to compete with the best and I have proved that a few times, I just need to show more consistency.” Selby is now in danger of losing his world number one spot for the first time since February 2015. If Mark Williams goes all the way to the title in York he will go top of the rankings. Leicester’s Selby said: “I was rubbish all match, I didn’t get going at all. I’m devastated because it’s a big tournament. I felt flat and couldn’t get myself up for the match which is strange because it’s such a big event. If I had potted the pink to go 4-2 I probably would have won because he was wilting at that stage. I have been playing really well lately so to perform like that is a real surprise for me.” World Champion Williams had no such trouble as he beat Adam Duffy 6-2 with a top break of 68. “This will probably be my last tournament of the year so I’ll try to have a good run,” said Williams. “The last few months have been a bit of a party for me. I’m going on holiday in December and then when I get back before the Masters I will have to knuckle down and get back to normal.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BetVictor Scottish Open Draw</title><link href="/project/2018/11/25/Scottish-draw.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BetVictor Scottish Open Draw" /><published>2018-11-25T11:39:07+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-25T11:39:07+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/25/Scottish-draw</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/25/Scottish-draw.html">&lt;h3&gt;BetVictor Scottish Open Draw&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/draw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    The tournament at the Glasgow Emirates runs from December 10 to 16 with 128 players battling for the Stephen Hendry Trophy.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Last year’s tremendous final saw Neil Robertson beat Cao Yupeng 9-8 in a dramatic conclusion. Also among the field were the likes of Ronnie O’Sullivan, Judd Trump, Mark Williams and home favourite John Higgins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The WORLD CUP OFFER gives fans the chance to buy all-day tickets for the first four days of the tournament (Monday December 10 to Thursday December 13) for just £10. And with the action taking place on up to eight tables at once, it’s an incredible chance to see a wide range of the best snooker stars on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the star names in the draw are Ronnie O’Sullivan, Judd Trump, Shaun Murphy, Mark Allen, Ding Junhui, home favourite John Higgins and defending champion Neil Robertson. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Televised by Eurosport and Quest, the Scottish Open is the third of the 2018/19 season’s Home Nations events, with the others in England, Northern Ireland and Wales. Once again there will be a £1 million bonus on offer to any player who can win all four Home Nations events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are available now and start at just £10 – for details click here.  Take advantage of our Black Friday offer with selected tickets at just £5! &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">BetVictor Scottish Open Draw The tournament at the Glasgow Emirates runs from December 10 to 16 with 128 players battling for the Stephen Hendry Trophy. Last year’s tremendous final saw Neil Robertson beat Cao Yupeng 9-8 in a dramatic conclusion. Also among the field were the likes of Ronnie O’Sullivan, Judd Trump, Mark Williams and home favourite John Higgins. The WORLD CUP OFFER gives fans the chance to buy all-day tickets for the first four days of the tournament (Monday December 10 to Thursday December 13) for just £10. And with the action taking place on up to eight tables at once, it’s an incredible chance to see a wide range of the best snooker stars on the planet. Among the star names in the draw are Ronnie O’Sullivan, Judd Trump, Shaun Murphy, Mark Allen, Ding Junhui, home favourite John Higgins and defending champion Neil Robertson. Televised by Eurosport and Quest, the Scottish Open is the third of the 2018/19 season’s Home Nations events, with the others in England, Northern Ireland and Wales. Once again there will be a £1 million bonus on offer to any player who can win all four Home Nations events. Tickets are available now and start at just £10 – for details click here. Take advantage of our Black Friday offer with selected tickets at just £5!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Watch snooker on Eurosport Player</title><link href="/project/2018/11/24/eurosport.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Watch snooker on Eurosport Player" /><published>2018-11-24T18:23:03+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-24T18:23:03+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/24/eurosport</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/24/eurosport.html">&lt;h3&gt;Watch snooker on Eurosport Player&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class='right' src=&quot;/project/img/post/eurosport.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Snooker fans throughout Europe can watch the sport anywhere and on any device on Eurosport Player, the leading live
    and on-demand digital sport platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eurosport Player is available to download and watch in 52 markets and in 20 languages, offering fans an all-access
    pass to immerse themselves in the greatest events on the global sporting calendar. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With live and on-demand content available any time, fans can experience sport in the way that they enjoy best and
    access enhanced live features, such as additional feeds and camera angles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fans across Europe can subscribe, with fantastic value for money and the chance to watch the best snooker stars on
    the planet battling for the most prestigious trophies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following events are available on Eurosport Player in 2018/19:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Betway UK Championship &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;November 27 to December 9, 2018 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;BetVictor Scottish Open&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;December 10-16, 2018 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Qualifiers: German Masters &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;December 18-21, 2018 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Dafabet Masters &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;January 13-20, 2019 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;D88.com German Masters &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;January 30 February 3, 2019 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Coral World Grand Prix &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;February 4-10, 2019 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;ManBetX Welsh Open &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;February 11-17, 2019 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;China Open qualifiers &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;February 18-21 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Shoot Out &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;February 21-24, 2019 &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Indian Open  &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;February 27 to March 3, 2019  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Watch snooker on Eurosport Player Snooker fans throughout Europe can watch the sport anywhere and on any device on Eurosport Player, the leading live and on-demand digital sport platform. Eurosport Player is available to download and watch in 52 markets and in 20 languages, offering fans an all-access pass to immerse themselves in the greatest events on the global sporting calendar. With live and on-demand content available any time, fans can experience sport in the way that they enjoy best and access enhanced live features, such as additional feeds and camera angles. Fans across Europe can subscribe, with fantastic value for money and the chance to watch the best snooker stars on the planet battling for the most prestigious trophies. The following events are available on Eurosport Player in 2018/19: Betway UK Championship November 27 to December 9, 2018 BetVictor Scottish Open December 10-16, 2018 Qualifiers: German Masters December 18-21, 2018 Dafabet Masters January 13-20, 2019 D88.com German Masters January 30 February 3, 2019 Coral World Grand Prix February 4-10, 2019 ManBetX Welsh Open February 11-17, 2019 China Open qualifiers February 18-21 Shoot Out February 21-24, 2019 Indian Open February 27 to March 3, 2019</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump I Need The Big Titles</title><link href="/project/2018/11/20/judd-trump.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump I Need The Big Titles" /><published>2018-11-20T18:23:03+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-20T18:23:03+02:00</updated><id>/project/2018/11/20/judd-trump</id><content type="html" xml:base="/project/2018/11/20/judd-trump.html">&lt;h3&gt;Trump – I Need The Big Titles &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Judd Trump hopes he can keep his hot streak of form going as he looks ahead to the Betway UK Championship in York.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Trump won last week’s Northern Ireland Open in Belfast, his first ranking title in over a year. He won seven matches, culminating in a superb 9-7 defeat of Ronnie O’Sullivan in the final.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;left&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/trymp1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    Bristol’s 29-year-old Trump won the UK Championship in York back in 2011 but that remains his only victory in a Triple Crown tournament. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I need to win the big events,” admitted the world number five. “I have got to the final stages of all of them but getting over the line makes a huge difference. You won’t be remembered for getting to a lot of quarter and semi-finals. Hopefully within the next couple of seasons I can tick off the Masters and the World Championship and then the Triple Crown will be out of the way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everyone has good spells during the season and now that I’m on a roll I don’t want it to stop. My game is improving and everything came together last week. It was the most I have ever enjoyed a tournament, I was relaxed and playing with a lot of freedom. Winning a title was well overdue for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The fans were amazing and their support was massive. In the final it was almost 50-50 between me and Ronnie. Someone would call out Ronnie’s name and then someone else would call back mine which was a nice feeling. People cheering me on really helps when I’m under pressure.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump lost 10-9 to O’Sullivan in the 2014 UK final in York &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;right&quot; src=&quot;/project/img/post/trymp2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    He added: “The likes of Ronnie, Mark Selby and Mark Williams have been dominating in recent years but they are three of the best five or six players of all time so it’s a tough era to play in now. There are good Chinese players coming through but none of them have the full package yet and until they do it will be the same players winning titles.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Betway UK Championship runs from November 27 to December 9 at the York Barbican, with 128 players battling for a top prize of £170,000. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump faces experienced amateur David Lilley in the first round on Tuesday November 27 at 7.30pm. Other top stars in action over the first three days include O’Sullivan, Selby, Williams, John Higgins, Mark Allen, Neil Robertson, Shaun Murphy and Ding Junhui. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Tickets for the first three days start at just £8, and with eight tables in play in every session, it’s an incredible chance for fans to see many of the world’s top stars with superb value for money.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Trump – I Need The Big Titles Judd Trump hopes he can keep his hot streak of form going as he looks ahead to the Betway UK Championship in York. Trump won last week’s Northern Ireland Open in Belfast, his first ranking title in over a year. He won seven matches, culminating in a superb 9-7 defeat of Ronnie O’Sullivan in the final. Bristol’s 29-year-old Trump won the UK Championship in York back in 2011 but that remains his only victory in a Triple Crown tournament. “I need to win the big events,” admitted the world number five. “I have got to the final stages of all of them but getting over the line makes a huge difference. You won’t be remembered for getting to a lot of quarter and semi-finals. Hopefully within the next couple of seasons I can tick off the Masters and the World Championship and then the Triple Crown will be out of the way. “Everyone has good spells during the season and now that I’m on a roll I don’t want it to stop. My game is improving and everything came together last week. It was the most I have ever enjoyed a tournament, I was relaxed and playing with a lot of freedom. Winning a title was well overdue for me. “The fans were amazing and their support was massive. In the final it was almost 50-50 between me and Ronnie. Someone would call out Ronnie’s name and then someone else would call back mine which was a nice feeling. People cheering me on really helps when I’m under pressure.” Trump lost 10-9 to O’Sullivan in the 2014 UK final in York He added: “The likes of Ronnie, Mark Selby and Mark Williams have been dominating in recent years but they are three of the best five or six players of all time so it’s a tough era to play in now. There are good Chinese players coming through but none of them have the full package yet and until they do it will be the same players winning titles.” The Betway UK Championship runs from November 27 to December 9 at the York Barbican, with 128 players battling for a top prize of £170,000. Trump faces experienced amateur David Lilley in the first round on Tuesday November 27 at 7.30pm. Other top stars in action over the first three days include O’Sullivan, Selby, Williams, John Higgins, Mark Allen, Neil Robertson, Shaun Murphy and Ding Junhui. Tickets for the first three days start at just £8, and with eight tables in play in every session, it’s an incredible chance for fans to see many of the world’s top stars with superb value for money.</summary></entry></feed>